♪ 如冒犯请指教 ♪
♪ If I'm off, please correct ♪
♪ 你挡着我道了 ♪
♪ You're standing on my neck ♪
拽妹Daria
漫迪字幕组&@Daria拽妹黛薇儿
——·@严肃活泼小kk译制·——
最后呢
And finally,
我们会和科学和语言艺术部门合作
we will be teaming up with the Science and Language Arts departments
进行一次跨专业学科的吉姆丛林彩弹之旅
for an interdisciplinary field trip to Jim's Paintballing Jungle.
你们中有些人可能会觉得这活动比上课睡觉还要费力
An activity that some of you may find more taxing than sleeping through class!
国际联盟吗?
Um... the League of Nations?
一战后成立的国际组织 二战后被联合国取代
那我们为什么去模拟实战呢?
And why are we going to engage in simulated combat?
Daria?
因为只有拿着玩具枪在树林里你追我赶
Because no high school education is complete until you've chased
高中教育才算完整吗?
your fellow students around the woods with toy guns?
你的挖苦让我发笑 Daria
Your sarcasm amuses me, Daria.
我希望你蜷缩在隐匿处时 那番话能抚慰你
I hope it provides you comfort when you're cowering in a foxhole.
不 我们是要去学习战争如何影响文化的各个方面
No, we're going to study how warfare impacts all aspects of culture.
现在 我们还需要一些家长志愿者
Now, we're going to need parent volunteers.
那就是说 如果他们有人
That is, if any of them can pull
能自愿舍弃六位数年薪不做马屁精的话
themselves away from their six figure jobs as sycophants!
怎么了 Kevin?
Yes, Kevin?
我爸不是马屁精 D老师 他是承包商
My dad's not a sycophant, Mr. D. He's a contractor!
Kevin 你要靠近射击范围的话就得和我待在一起 行吗 孩子?
Kevin, stay close to me when you get to the paintball range, okay, son?
行
Sure!
鱼类是把我们的海洋当成他们的私鱼厕所了吗?
Are fish using our oceans as their own private toilet?
呕心小世界独家节目 即将为您播出
A Sick, Sad World exclusive, right after this.
厕所在走廊最里边 另外大海在那边
The bathroom's down the hall, or there's an ocean that way.
这房间比我记忆中还让人讨厌
Ugh. This room is even geekier then I remembered.
对不起 最大的入住率是原因之一
I'm sorry, the maximum occupancy is one.
请从前门离开
Please exit through the front.
听着 我知道你喜欢让我难堪还 要说一些我俩很亲近的话
Look, I know how you like to embarrass me and say we're related and stuff,
可拜托你不要和爸妈说
but please don't tell Mom and Dad
学校需要彩弹志愿者的事好吗?
that they're looking for paintball volunteers, okay?
可我已经给他们发了邀请函啦
But I already sent out their invitations.
呵呵 你才没有呢 对吧?
Ha ha. You didn't, right?
淡定 我们因同一个目标而协同共进:
Relax. We work together for the sake of a common goal:
就是我们谁都不要提彩弹或志愿者的事
no mention of paintballing or volunteering from either one of us.
同意
Agreed.
然后呢 等我们达成目标以后
Later, after we have achieved this goal,
我们将恢复那种长久以来
we'll resume the age-old hostilities
都不可能在这房子里产生和平的敌意
that have made peace in this region of the house a seeming impossibility.
好计划
Good plan.
Quinn?
你是不是觉得这发型暗示着什么?
Do you think this hair style means something?
因为它压根没暗示什么
Because it doesn't.
可你从来不....
But you never...
我就不能随心所欲试试新造型吗?
Can't I experiment with a new look if I want to?
当然可以 但我...
Of course, but I...
好呗 好呗
All right, all right!
全校要去一个彩弹野战赛
The whole school's going on a paintballing field trip.
把火钳收起来
Put away the red-hot poker.
时尚俱乐部要我负责找到一种能防止头发被头盔压塌的发型
The Fashion Club put me in charge of figuring out a style to prevent helmet hair.
我不知道她们要这样做的 我承受不住所有压力
I didn't know they were going to do it! I can't take all this pressure...
别自责了 你好好挺住十秒钟
Don't beat yourself up. You held out a good ten seconds.
彩弹 多激动人心啊 对吧 Daria?
Paintballing! That's exciting, isn't it, Daria?
不
No.
Daria 这趟出行对你来说会很有益的
Daria, this trip would be very good for you.
你能了解自己的校友和老师
You'll get to know your schoolmates and your teachers.
我嗅到那会有很多大学的推荐信
I smell lots of recommendations for college!
真好笑
That's funny.
我只能嗅到十五磅的魔法编织牌发胶味
All I smell is fifteen pounds of Magic Braid hair gel.
那些信对你进入第一志愿的学校关系重大
Those letters can make the difference in getting into your first choice school.
只有在你有第一志愿时才关系重大
Only if you have a first choice school.
- Jake 告诉Daria - 我的天啊
- Jake, tell Daria... - Oh, my God,
我得去修一路坏到家里另一头的松塌地板啦
I have to fix that loose floorboard all the way at the other end of the house.
事实上 我可能要亲自去和那些老师聊一聊
Actually, I should probably deal with these teachers directly.
嘿 你是想帮我念完这学期吗?
Hey, do you want to finish out the semester for me?
这可是一个负责任家长该做的事
It's what an involved parent would do.
妈 我觉得你已经证明你有参与其中啦
Mom, I think you've already demonstrated your involvement
每次O'Neill老师找你去家长会
by pretending you're going out of town
你都假装出差啦
whenever Mr. O'Neill calls about school review meetings.
那个男的太.... 恐怖了嘛
That man is just so... creepy.
我觉得他们不需要志愿者去....
I don't suppose they need volunteers for this...
不需要
No!
噢 该死
Oh, darn!
好吧
All right!
现在让我们瞧瞧车上的哪一边唱的最大声
Now lets see which side of the bus can sing the loudest!
左边
Left side!
"当Johnny迈步回家时 万岁 万岁"
"When Johnny comes marching home again, hurrah, hurrah!"
美国独立战争歌曲《当约翰尼迈步回家时》
来嘛 右边 别害羞
Come on, left side, don't be shy.
谢谢你 O'Neill老师
Thank you, Mr. O'Neill,
谢谢你不知疲倦的奉献和提醒学生我们有多老土
for your tireless dedication to reminding the students how out of touch we are.
接下来 我们来讨论一下游击战的历史
Now, we're going to discuss the history of guerilla warfare.
"离大白鲨只有20米"
"Only 20 miles to the Great White Shark."
你知道吗 鲨鱼其实不喜欢吃人
You know, sharks don't really like to eat humans.
他们通常都只是浅尝辄止就游走了
They usually just tear out a bite and swim away.
和我妹妹的约会情况真像
Very much like my sister's dates.
我是说 当然啦 他们通常会咬走一两个重要器官...
I mean, sure, they often take a vital organ or two with them...
我很感激你试着安慰我 不过这并不凑效
I appreciate you trying to cheer me up, but it's not going to work.
来嘛 我们来玩单词游戏嘛
Come on! Let's play a word game!
地理怎么样?
How about geography?
不 你得玩你知道的东西
Nah, you have to, like, know stuff for that.
玩地产大亨咋样?
What about Monopoly?
地产大亨不是单词游戏
Monopoly isn't a word game.
我知道啊
I know that.
我能当赛车吗?
Can I be the racing car?
那就这样做吧
So it's decided:
不管发生什么事 我们都不要对彼此开枪也不要弄脏衣服
no matter what happens, we won't shoot each other and mess up our outfits.
如果我对某个时尚俱乐部的成员开火了
If I fire on a fellow Fashion Club member,
我就得穿一个星期棕色的橡皮筋裤子
may I wear brown pants with an elastic band for a whole week.
如果我开火了 我就穿灰褐色的裤袜 还是闪亮的那种
If I fire, I'll wear taupe pantyhose. The shiny kind.
我就穿砂洗牛仔裤
Stonewashed jeans.
我戴眼镜
Glasses.
Quinn 不要担心有人会伤害你 因为我会保护你的
Quinn, don't worry about anyone hitting you. Cause I'll protect you.
我也是 我是你的保镖
Me, too! I'll be your bodyguard!
他们得先杀了我
They'll have to kill me first.
好吧
Well, okay!
我是真心想为你挡子弹
I really want to take a bullet for you
如果你挡得了的话
Oh, if only you could.
此地距离大白鲨只有10英里
好的 所以就轮到Mack了
Okay, so let's say it's Mack's turn.
他说"我从没一脚踏两船"
He says, "I never went steady with two people at the same time."
然后Jodie 要是你从来没有脚踏两船的话 你不用喝酒
And then Jodie, if you never went steady with two people at the same time,
你不用喝酒
then you don't take a drink.
喝什么酒啊? 我们在车上
A drink of what? We're on a bus.
可我的意思是 要是我有一脚踏两船的话
But I, like, have gone steady with two people at the same time,
我就得罚酒 懂了吗?
so I do take a drink. Get it?
那个 我是说... 不好
Oh, I... I mean... oh no.
距离大白鲨还有1英里
拜托
Come on!
我们甩掉彩弹野战去拜访大白鲨吧
Let's ditch paintballing and go visit the Great White Shark.
会很酷的
It'll be cool.
不 才不酷呢 会很蠢的 况且我们已经在做蠢事了
No, it won't. It'll be stupid, and we're already doing something stupid.
可那蠢事会是我们的主意
But this stupid thing will be our idea.
没兴趣
Not interested.
现在这里就有很多白痴的史前生物
There are plenty of tiny-brained prehistoric creatures right here.
吉姆丛林彩弹
惊喜咯
Surprise!
他们来干嘛?
What are they doing here?
我猜是在家里私下折磨我还不够吧
I guess tormenting me in the privacy of my own home wasn't enough.
Daria 这不是很好吗?
Daria, isn't this great?
我之前和你妈妈说了家长会的事
I called your mother about the school review,
可她那晚出差了
but she was going out of town that night
而且还问起我们是不是需要志愿者
and asked if we were looking for paintball volunteers!
我只希望有更多的家长
I only wish more parents
能对"积极参与孩子的教育"这事足够重视
cared enough to take such an active role in their children education.
我也是
Me, too!
是啊...
Yes...
要是我们走得快一点 十点钟就能看到大白鲨啦
If we walk fast, we can see the Great White Shark by ten.
吉姆丛林彩弹大型运动场
我们也有一个战俘监狱的复制品 臭名昭著的河内希尔顿
We also have an exact replica of 'nam's infamous POW prison, the Hanoi Hilton.
可享受特殊的婚礼折扣
Special discouts for weddings.
上校吗?
Colonel, or whatever.
请问女厕所在哪?
Where's the ladies room?
噢 那是有分布着一些慰安所
Oh, there are "comfort stations" scattered about,
不过都伪装的很好啦
but they're really well camouflaged.
嘿 你 过来
Hey, you! Come here!
我?
Me?
瞧好了
Watch this!
Jake
Jake!
是不是很厉害? 一整条迷宫状的地下通道
Isn't it great? A whole labyrinth of underground tunnels.
你能在里面迷失好几天
You could get lost down there for days.
嗯 真厉害 有虫
Yeah, great. Uck, worms!
抓住这个难得的机会 大声说
So, seize this golden opportunity to say,
"年轻人私密汇报 先生或女士
"Private Young Person reporting, sir or madam,
准备好愿意探索团队精神的真正意义了吗"
ready, willing, and able to explore the true meaning of teamwork."
出发 团队
Let's go, team!
没错 Brittany
That's it, Brittany!
红队里有谁想在出发前说点什么吗?
Who else on Team Red wants to say something before we begin?
Jane...?
Jane 这时候团队里可没有"自我"这一说
Now, Jane, there's no "I" in team.
闭嘴
Oh, shut up!
为了理解战争对自然社会的破坏性
To understand the disruptive nature of war on society,
我们首先得理解它对个人的震撼影响
first we must understand its shattering impact on individuals.
尽管这么假设很愚蠢
I realize it's foolish of me to assume that
蓝队里的任何一员都知道切肤之痛是什么感觉
any member of Team Blue even knows what physical pain feels like,
像被纸割一样无关痛痒
outside of a paper cut!
对呀 真是一群...
Yeah, what a bunch of... ahh!
对不起 警报有误
Sorry. False alarm!
没关系
That's okay.
那就是你叔叔?
Eww, that's your uncle?
好了 记住游戏的目的就是开枪杀戮
Now, remember the object of the game is to shoot to kill.
不好意思 游戏的目的不是夺得敌人的旗帜么?
Excuse me. Isn't the object of the game to capture the enemy's flag?
随便啦 行动开始
Whatever. Move out!
好的 在我们上战场之前
Now, before we go out on the battlefield,
有没有谁想分享一下他的感受...
would anyone like to share their feelings with...
既然O'Neill老师如所预见般抛弃了我们
Now that Mr. O'Neill has predictably deserted us in our prime,
现在到我指挥
I will take command.
好啦 如果我们分散成长排向队旗进攻...
All right, if we spread out in a long line and sweep towards the flag...
打扰一下 Barche老师?
Excuse me, Ms. Barch?
既然我们有地势优势
Since they can't see us very well because of the terrain,
我们就能分散行动 他们也发现不了我们
we can split up and they won't know where we are,
然后我们能从三方进攻
then we can attack them from three sides,
把他们逼到他们以为是安全的死角
drive them out to the one side that they think is safe,
在那里设下埋伏 就能把他们一网打尽
and then set up an ambush so we can capture them all at once!
也许在高地设一个秘密瞭望点会是一个好主意
Probably be a good idea to set up a secret observation post on the high ground
这样就能在他们发现不了的情况下监视他们
so we can watch them without them seeing us.
怎么啦?
What?
真是好极了 Brittany
That's very good, Brittany.
好的 蓝队 出发
Okay, team, let's go!
来嘛 Jane
Come on Jane!
我更像是个雇佣兵
I'm more of the mercenary type.
你懂的 我喜欢单刀匹马自己干
You know, lone wolf working on their own type of thing.
太好了
Good idea.
如果A计划黄了 你还能执行拯救任务呢
If Plan A fails, you can come in on a rescue mission!
那个男人在开枪
The men are shooting!
那些彩弹打人好痛啊
Ow! Those paintball thingies hurt.
不 你被打中了
Oh, no, you're hit.
你出局了
You're out of the game.
好吧
Oh, well.
可怜的孩子 打从一开始就没有机会
Poor kid. She never had a chance.
谁谁在电影里有句台词说 地狱就是理智的可能性
Somebody in a movie once said, hell is the possibility of sanity.
这就是这地方给我的感受
That's what this place feels like.
真该死 我已经开始讨厌这儿了
Hell. I hate it already.
才过了一个小时
And it's only been an hour.
该死的时间 奶奶
Some damn hour, Grandma.
Daria 你至少回击一下吧
Daria, you could at least try.
我不能朝我亲生母亲开枪 至少不能用油彩呀
I can't shoot my own mother. Not with paint, anyway.
Daria 我放弃一切来到这里
Daria, I'm out here giving my all.
你哪怕就一次...
Why can't you for once...
Helen Morgendorffer
Helen Morgendorffer!
噢 嗨 Eric
Oh, hi, Eric!
是啊 我是在森林中部呢 你能相信吗?
Yes, I'm out here in the middle of the woods, can you believe it?
便签吗? Stephanie没有把它给你吗?
The memo? Didn't Stephanie give it to you?
很抱歉
Sorry.
什么事耽误你这么久?
What took you so long?
我半路杀了一个村的农民
I stopped to wipe out a village of farmers.
我说 就因为你为了他帅哥哥甩了他这事
I mean, just because you dump a guy for his older, cuter brother,
他就对你怀恨在心啦?
does that give him the right to hold a grudge?
男人还真是有够不成熟的呢
Men are so immature.
你造吗 要是我早知道我们要在泥地跋涉
You know, if I knew we were going to be running around in the dirt,
我就不会穿名牌运动鞋来
I wouldn't have worn my good sneakers.
你们能闭嘴吗? 我好像看到什么了
Will you guys shut up? I think I see something.
嘿 Quinn 那是你表姐吗?
Hey, Quinn, is that your cousin?
就该这么做 Quinn队长
Way to go, Quinn. Our leader!
嘿 这是我新买的
Hey, I just bought this.
Sandi? 你在这儿干嘛?
Sandi? What are you doing here?
我在找厕所呢 你突然就朝我开枪了
I was looking for the bathroom, and all of a sudden you started shooting at me.
我以为我们说好不开火的
I thought we promised not to do that.
我不会朝你开枪的 Sandi
I would never fire at you, Sandi.
可你戴了防护镜 我没认出来
I didn't recognize you with your goggles.
就是呀 你干嘛要穿那个啊? 丑死了
Yeah, I mean, why are you wearing them? They're so ugly.
因为规定就是要穿啊
Because those are the rules.
好嘛 有些规定就是制定来让人违反的
Well, some rules are made to be broken,
就比如穿橘色毛衣还要烈焰红唇那样
like wearing red lipstick with an orange sweater.
还有金头发还要画烟熏妆
Or black mascara with blond hair.
再说了 你都中弹了 还要打我们
Besides, you fired on us when you were already hit,
这也有违规则
and that's against the rules, too.
没错
Yeah.
老天 要是你们都帮着Quinn
Gee, if everyone's on Quinn's side,
干脆让Quinn做时尚俱乐部的主席得了
maybe Quinn should be president of the Fashion Club.
别傻了 我才不会做主席呢
Don't be silly. I would never try to be president,
只要一天有你在 都不会
as long as you were around.
真哒?
Really?
没错 你真的觉得我能取代你吗?
Sure. I mean, do you really think that I could replace you?
好了 Kevin 你觉得你那个萎缩的豌豆般大的细胞体
Okay, Kevin, do you think that atrophied, pea-sized cluster of cells
就是你说的"脑子"
that you refer to as your brain
能记住我刚给你下达的复杂指令吗?
can remember the complicated instructions I just gave you?
嗯... 夺得队旗?
Um... "get the flag"?
很好 Kevin
Very good, Kevin.
不准动 宝贝
Freeze, babe.
那彩弹打人真疼啊
Ow! Those paintball thingies hurt!
我都要上绷带啦
I'm going to get a welt!
战争就是残酷的 Kevvy
War's not pretty, Kevvy.
抱歉喽
Sorry.
烂死了 坏骗子 你们都是骗子
Rotten, dirtbag liars! All of you!
Barch老师 别打啦 彩弹打人可疼啦
Ms. Barch, stop shooting! Those paintball thingies hurt!
亏我还相信你 该死
I trusted you, dammit!
整整二十年的合法奴隶制
Two decades of legal slavery,
你还是为一件系带背心和一双小舞鞋就把它抛之脑后啦
and still you throw it all away for a halter top and a pair of pumps!
夫人 我想你一定是认错人啦
Madam, I believe you've got me confused with someone else!
我可不是你前夫
I'm not your ex-husband!
我知道 可他不在这儿
I know that, but he's not here!
距离大白鲨还有3英里
很好 之前我还一直觉得太干燥了
Good. I was feeling too dry.
也许我们该调头
Maybe we should turn back.
也许你妈妈会借给你一件雨衣
Maybe your mother will lend you a raincoat.
乖乖闭嘴走下去吧
Shut up and keep walking.
大白鲨
我们是来看大白鲨的
We're here to see the Great White Shark.
那就是杰作 不是吗?
Oh, it's a beauty, ain't it?
请勿触摸
那就是颗牙齿
It's a tooth.
如果你知道大白鲨的传说 就不会说它只是颗牙齿了
You wouldn't say, "it's a tooth," if you know the legend of Great White.
长久以来 女人就是被设定成要隐瞒自己年龄的
Woman have been programmed to lie about their age for so long,
怪不得人们说四十岁看起来像五十岁
no wonder people think forty looks like fifty.
我很欣慰那结束了
I'm glad that's over.
阿门 感谢上帝 男人不再把我们看作是发泄兽欲的对象
Amen! Thank God men no longer look at us like sex objects.
言之有理 妹子
You said it, sister.
那我看起来是不是有46... 44岁?
So do I look forty si... four?
- 介意我... - 想都别想 你这男人
- Would you like my... - Forget it, you man!
可我只是想给你我的...
But I was just offering my...
浪费老娘22年青春 一走了之
Twenty two years of my life, gone!
你所展现出来的照顾
And all I have to show for tending to your every need
就只有我脚上的鸡眼和胸上的皮疹
are the corns on my feet and a big rash on my chest.
继续 没关系的 都发泄出来
Go ahead, it's all right. Let it out.
噢 你为什么不带着你的好战性
Oh, why don't you just go back outside
出去破坏些脆弱的东西
with your war mongering sex and destroy something weak.
宣泄会让你感觉良好 是吧?
Venting feels good, doesn't it?
你绝对有权利感到愤怒 并释放出来
You have every right to feel angry, and to express that anger.
嗨 外面倾盆大雨呢
Hi! It's raining cats and dogs out there!
在这种情况下是多么独特的视角
What a unique perspective on the situation.
喝点暖暖身吗?
Little nip to warm you up?
Morgendorffer先生 我是一名教师
Mr. Morgendorffer, I'm a teacher,
要在一次相当危险的实地考察中对学生负责
responsible for dozens of students on a fairly hazardous filed trip.
你觉得我能喝吗?
Do you think I should take a little nip?
我想还是算了吧
I guess not.
不 我想还是不要算了 快给我
No, I guess not! Gimme that!
话说你是不是上过军校呀?
Say, did you, by any chance, go to military school?
你怎么知道?
How'd you know that?!
在大白鲨被捕的两个月以前
Until Great White was captured two months ago,
他威吓东海岸
he terrorized the eastern seaboard,
把旅客嚼进嘴里 又像喝了坏红酒那样把他们吐出来
chomping on tourists and spitting them out like bad red wine.
好极了
Excellent.
那是旅游旺季
It was the peak of tourist season,
当一具残缺的尸体被冲上海岸时
when a mangled body washed up on the shore,
沙滩上的流浪者都吓坏了...
scaring the beachcombers...
河内希尔顿
你更喜欢我们俩中的谁?
Which one of us do you like best?
你们谁想带我去Chez Pierre夜店?
Which one of you wants to take me to Chez Pierre?
我带你去
I'll take you!
不不 我来 我有钱
No, no, me! I've got the money!
Quinn真是太萌了
Quinn's so cute.
对啊
Yeah.
比我还萌?
Cuter than me?
不是啦 你萌多了啦
Oh, no. You're way cuter.
外表不是最重要的
Not that looks are important.
没错
No way.
我希望我能找到厕所
I wish I could find that bathroom.
应该是在那边的某个地方
I think it's over there somewhere.
Sandi去哪啦?
Where's Sandi?
你懂的啦 Sandi嘛 总是去找厕所的路上
Oh, you know Sandi. Always looking for a bathroom.
她今天特别萌
She looks really cute today.
比我还萌吗?
Cuter than me?
不是啦 你萌多了嘛
Oh, no. You're way cuter.
当然啦
Of course,
市长称那些残骸都是螺旋桨的受害者
the mayor claimed that the chewed-up bodies were the victims of a propeller,
但老百姓才不会上当
but the people knew better.
不好意思呀 这不是电影《大白鲨》的桥段吗?
Excuse me, but isn't this the plot of Jaws?
不不 这完全不同呢
No, no! This is completely different.
就在那时他们把捕鲨人叫来了
That's when they called in the great shark hunter.
就在那时他们叫来了... 我
That's when they called in... me.
Morgendorffer太太 看到你如此关心你的女儿们 我很欣慰
I'm glad to see you take such an interest in your daughters, Mrs. Morgendorffer.
独自养大两个青少年真的很不容易... 还是和Jake一起
Well, it isn't easy raising two teenagers all by yourself... with Jake.
当然啦 我觉得学校环境也是很重要的因素
Of course, I like to think the school environment also plays a pivotal role.
没错
Absolutely.
虽然给予学生更多一点鼓励会更好
Although it would be nice if the students got a little more encouragement.
也许像Daria这么聪明的孩子态度就会更好了
Maybe a bright kid like Daria would have a better attitude.
我说了什么那么好笑?
Did I say something funny?
恕我直言
With all due respect,
我想象不出有什么监狱能培养出令千金那种态度了
I can't think of a prison that could create an attitude like your daughter's,
更别说学校
much less a school.
不 我经常假设这是源于和父母的互动 或是缺乏交流
No, I always assumed that came from interaction with her parents, or lack of it.
噢 所以按你这么说 监狱和学校是有区别的喽
Oh, so you draw a distinction between prison and school.
因为据我知 你把学校搞的和监狱差不多
Because from what I've heard, you run the one pretty much like the other.
我压根不用听这话
I don't have to listen to this!
是 你是不用
No, you don't!
顺便多说一句 你看起来有50岁
And by the way, you look fifty!
我试过用鱼叉捕它
I tried harpooning Great White,
但那巨兽像甩牙签一样把鱼叉甩掉了
but the massive beast shook them off like so many toothpicks.
我试过用浮桶把它拖下来 可还是不行
I tried tying him down with floating barrels, but no.
大白鲨说"我才不受这些控制" 所以船长就决定...
Great White said, "I will have none of this!" So the captain decided...
雨小点儿了 我们走吧
The rain's letting up. Let's get out of here.
然后那小鼻涕虫Richard Dreyfuss决定他自己要露一手....
Then that little snot Richard Dreyfuss decides that it was all his big game...
和另一半签订婚前协议前 不先和自己签一份
Just what good is signing a prenuptial agreement with another
又有什么意义呢?
if we don't first sign one with ourselves?
我从来没想过会有这种事
I never thought it possible.
你真体恤 尽管你是个男人
You're sensitive, yet you're a male.
噢 好吧...
Oh, well, ...
小心皮疹...
Watch the rash...
我是不想重蹈我爸的覆辙
I didn't mean to step on Dad's contact.
第二天 他就把我送去军校了
The next day, he shipped me off to military school!
我妈不想让她的情夫们知道她有个拖油瓶
My mother didn't want her dates to know she had a son,
所以我经常待在邻居家 奇怪又扭曲的邻居
so I spent a lot of time at the neighbors. Strange, twisted people!
我懂 我也有这样的邻居
I know! I had the same neighbors!
Jake 你喝醉了
Jake! You're drunk!
醉了? 别傻啦
Drunk? Don't be silly!
Quinn 快来
Quinn, come on!
Quinn 我们要走啦
Quinn! We're leaving!
回来呀 Quinn
Come back Quinn!
Quinn 快回来
Quinn! Come back!
"当Jonny迈步回家的时候 万岁 万岁"
"When Johnny comes marching home again, hurrah, hurrah..."
好啦 每个人都到齐了吗?
All right, is everyone accounted for?
好的 那就准备走吧
Yes. Okay, time to go!
等等 我没看到你们爸妈
Wait! I don't see the Morgendorffers.
好吧 那你又能怎么办
Oh, well, what can you do.
再说了 他们是自己开车来的
Besides, they drove here.
他们能自己开车回去
They can drive themselves home.
当然 如果没人把他们的分火盖偷走的话
That is, if someone hadn't taken their distributor cap.
等等
Wait!
当你要告诉妹子们你会对她们有所承诺
Drinking on a school trip when you're supposed
你就得在全校出游时期喝酒
to be showing the girls that you're committed!
承诺? 我承诺过 好啦 我是从来没受过考验啦
Committed? Oh, I've been committed, all right, and I never even had a trial!
等我有足够空间来重装子弹
Just wait till I have enough room to reload!
别啊 Helen 彩弹打得我好痛啊
No! Helen! Those paintball thingies hurt!
真可怕... 好可怕...
The horror... the horror...
欢迎微博关注
@漫迪字幕组